<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="city_name">Berlin</string>

    <string name="details_title">Details</string>
    <string name="categories_title">Categories</string>
    <string name="about_section_title">About</string>
    <string name="details_section_title">Details</string>
    <string name="details_address_title">Address:</string>

    <string name="details_phone_title">Phone:</string>
    <string name="details_call_btn">Call</string>
    <string name="details_directions_btn">Get Directions</string>

    <string name="main">See Guide</string>
    <string name="cat_monuments">Monuments</string>
    <string name="cat_parks">Parks</string>
    <string name="cat_hotels">Hotels</string>

    <string name="cd_back_btn">Back Button</string>
    <string name="cd_header_img">Header Image</string>
    <string name="cd_header_ovrl">Header Overlay</string>
    <string name="cd_content_bg">Content Background</string>
    <string name="cd_category_item_bg">Category Item Background</string>
    <string name="cd_category_item_arr">Open Item</string>
    <string name="cd_main_bg_img">Main Background Image</string>
    <string name="cd_fancy_btn">Fancy Button Icon</string>


    <string-array name="monuments_names">
        <item>Brandenburg Gate</item>
        <item>Victory Column (Siegessaule)</item>
        <item>St. George and the Dragon Statue</item>
        <item>Schiller Monument</item>
        <item>Bismarck-Nationadenkmal</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="monuments_addresses">
        <item>Pariser Platz, 10117 Berlin, Germany</item>
        <item>Grosser Stern 1, 10557 Berlin Germany</item>
        <item>Spreeufer 4 Spreeufer Intersection With Propststrasse, 10178 Berlin Germany</item>
        <item>Gendarmenmarkt Vor dem Schauspielhaus, 10117 Berlin Germany</item>
        <item>Grosser Stern 15, 10557 Berlin Germany</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="monuments_descriptions">
        <item>The Brandenburg Gate is 26 metres high, 65.5 metres long and 11 metres deep, and supported by two rows of six Doric columns. In 1793, the gate was crowned by the Quadriga statue, designed by Johann Gottfried Schadow. This statue also has its own story to tell.</item>
        <item>The victory column was built in 1873 to celebrate victory of Prussia in the Franco-German War. It was moved to its present location in the Tiergarten in 1938. You can go to the top via 270 steps to see great views of Berlin.</item>
        <item>The scale of the sculpture is larger-than-life. It depicts St. George on horseback, fighting with the dragon. The saint has pierced the dragon with his lance, which is broken, and has drawn his sword and holds it aloft to strike the dragon.</item>
        <item>It honors the poet, philosopher and historian Friedrich Schiller, who is also regarded as one of the most significant dramatists and lyricists of the German language. The set of statues was executed by Reinhold Begas a prominent 19th-century German sculptor. It is a registered historic monument.</item>
        <item>The Bismarck Memorial (German: Bismarck-Nationaldenkmal) is a prominent memorial statue in the Tiergarten in Berlin dedicated to Prince Otto von Bismarck, Minister President of the Kingdom of Prussia and the first Chancellor of the German Empire.It is one of 250 memorials to Bismarck worldwide.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="monuments_phones">
        <item>+49-30-2500-2333</item>
        <item>+49 30 3339509</item>
        <item></item>
        <item>21 317 9661</item>
        <item>21 315 8207</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="parks_names">
        <item>Charlottenburg Palace Gardens</item>
        <item>Görlitzer Park</item>
        <item>Lustgarten</item>
        <item>Viktoriapark</item>
        <item>Britzer Garten</item>
        <item>Tiergarten</item>
        <item>Gardens of the world (Gärten der Welt)</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="parks_addresses">
        <item>Spandauer Damm 10 14059 Berlin</item>
        <item>Görlitzer Straße 47 10997 Berlin</item>
        <item>Lustgarten 10178 Berlin</item>
        <item>Kreuzbergstr. 15 10965 Berlin</item>
        <item>Sangerhauser Weg 1 12349 Berlin</item>
        <item>Straße des 17. Juni 10557 Berlin</item>
        <item>Eisenacher Str. 99 12685 Berlin</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="parks_descriptions">
        <item>Stretching northwards from Charlottenburg Palace in the western city of Berlin, the garden welcomes visitors with a royal splendour and richness rarely found across the city. Mixing baroque elements with characteristics of the English landscape garden, the popular destination for Berliners and tourists alike is an outstanding example of Prussian garden design with winding paths, picturesque ponds and stunning views made for relaxation and contemplation rather than outdoors pursuits.</item>
        <item>Well-known across Berlin for its rough but unique Kreuzbergian charme, Görlitzer Park is the district\'s central recreational area. The park was laid out in the late 1980s and early 1990s on the grounds of the former Görlitzer Bahnhof station between Wiener Straße and Görlitzer Straße in the eastern part of Kreuzberg. Today only a few remaining tracks, remains of a pedestrian tunnel and three converted freight sheds remind visitors of the park\'s history.</item>
        <item>The Lustgarten (Pleasure Garden) is a quiet lawn, popular during the warmer season and well liked by tourists and Berliners alike as a pleasant bit of greenery to rest and lounge in at leisure. It is situated in front of the Altes Museum – the oldest museum in the Museumsinsel (Museum Island) ensemble between Karl-Liebknecht Straße, Kupfergraben and the majestic Berliner Dom (Cathedral).</item>
        <item>For a good 100 years only the Viktoriapark satisfied the longing for green in the Kreuzberg sea of houses. Fortunately, this is no longer the case today. But despite numerous alternatives, the park is still popular and well visited. During peak hours, tables and chairs for the family picnic are already in the pond, and in the central beer garden, the famous neighborhood nights are as long as ever. In rainy weather, however, romantics get their money\'s worth.</item>
        <item>The Britzer Garten in the south of Berlin is not only a delight for flowers and garden lovers. This excellent green area inspires a wide public with its variety. Hardly any other park changes its face so much with the changing seasons. The special shows in spring and late summer, which pamper the eye with a colourful sea of flowers made of tulips and dahlias respectively, are among the highlights of Berlin\'s calendar of events.</item>
        <item>Berliners make good use of the park for outdoor activities, sports and football games and grilling on Sundays is very popular. A large playground or Spielplatz is located on the southeastern corner near Potsdamer Platz. Some winters it is even possible to skate on the small lakes inside the park if weather conditions allow.</item>
        <item>When Berlin and Beijing signed the agreement on a city partnership in 1994, this marked the birth of the Chinese Garden. The "Garden of the Recovered Moon" was created according to plans of the Beijing Institute of Classical Garden Architecture. The entire construction was made with materials from China by skilled workers from Beijing. As a classical Chinese scholarly garden, the garden is characterised by simplicity and subtle colours - primarily grey, white and red. Its centre is a 4,500 square metre lake. The most outstanding building is the tea house, called "Berghaus zum Osmanthussaft", which is connected to other typical Chinese buildings by riverside paths and a zigzag bridge.</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="parks_phones">
        <item>030 32 09 11</item>
        <item></item>
        <item>21 224 5860</item>
        <item>21 224 5860</item>
        <item> </item>
        <item> </item>
        <item>21 410 2550</item>
    </string-array>



    <string-array name="hotels_names">
        <item>Park Inn by Radisson Berlin Alexanderplatz</item>
        <item>Sana Berlin Hotel</item>
        <item>nhow Berlin</item>
        <item>Living Hotel Großer Kurfürst</item>
        <item>Arcotel John F Berlin</item>
        <item>Steigenberger Hotel Berlin</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="hotels_addresses">
        <item>Alexanderplatz 7, 10178 Berlin</item>
        <item>Nuernberger Str. 33-34, 10777 Berlin</item>
        <item>Stralauer Allee 3, 10245 Berlin</item>
        <item>Neue Roßstraße 11-12, 10179 Berlin</item>
        <item>Werderscher Markt 11, 10117 Berlin</item>
        <item>Los-Angeles-Platz 1, 10789 Berlin</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="hotels_descriptions">
        <item>Radisson Hotel Group is implementing the Radisson Hotels Safety Protocol, a new program of in-depth cleanliness and disinfection procedures, in partnership with SGS, the world\’s leading Health and Safety inspection company. </item>
        <item>Benefiting from a central location in Berlin, close to the Tiergarten Park, the Zoo, the famous KaDeWe department store and the main commercial artery of the former West Berlin - Kurfrstendamm - SANA Berlin Hotel is uniquely designed for visitors</item>
        <item>Located right on the bank of the Spree, the nhow Berlin is just a short distance from Berlin Tegel Airport and Berlin Central Station. The nhow Berlin has many nearby attractions. Guests will find that the Oberbaumbrücke, the Arena Badeschiff, and the Ratibortheater are all within walking distance.</item>
        <item>With a stay at Living Hotel Großer Kurfürst, you will be centrally located in Berlin, a 10-minute walk from Nikolaikirche and 14 minutes by foot from DDR Museum. Featured amenities include a computer station, complimentary newspapers in the lobby, and dry cleaning/laundry services.</item>
        <item>With a stay at ARCOTEL John F Berlin, you will be centrally located in Berlin, within a 5-minute walk of Friedrichstrasse and Berlin State Opera. Featured amenities include complimentary newspapers in the lobby, dry cleaning/laundry services, and a 24-hour front desk.</item>
        <item>With a stay at Steigenberger Hotel Berlin, you will be centrally located in Berlin, steps from Kurfürstendamm and within a 5-minute walk of Kaiser Wilhelm Memorial Church. Featured amenities include a 24-hour business center, limo/town car service, and express check-out.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="hotels_phones">
        <item>787 584 104</item>
        <item>787 584 104</item>
        <item>787 584 104</item>
        <item>787 584 104</item>
        <item>787 584 104</item>
        <item>787 584 104</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="placeholder_name">National Museum of German History</string>
    <string name="placeholder_address">Calea Victoriei 12, Berlin</string>
    <string name="placeholder_description">The National Museum of German History is a museum located on Calea Victoriei, which contains historical artifacts from prehistoric times up to modern times.</string>
    <string name="placeholder_phone">+49 21 315 8208</string>
    <string name="placeholder_category_title">Category</string>

</resources>
